In this video, I'm going to show you how to create a square with a diameter of 750mm and a height of 750mm with a 2D window.
After selecting the rectangular tool, click on the 2D window to create a square with a width of 750mm and a height of 750mm.
Since the whole process of making a triangle is in a vertical form, in order to make it more convenient to use the function of shrinkage, we need to rotate the board first.
Drag the point on the frame to rotate the board to the position of the picture.
Because the board generated in the software is automatically generated when the fabric direction is created.
In order to make it convenient to use the elastic band shrinkage control fabric, we need to match the direction of the gusset and the board.
Use the inner line tool to create a folding line.
Click on the starting point, double click on the end point.
On the board, click on the right button to select the 2D arrangement position.
You can arrange it to the same position as the 2D window.
Next, let's flip the triangle board.
Before we make the gusset, we will keep it in a folding state.
Use the folding arrangement tool to select the inner line and drag the corresponding axis to fold the board.
Be careful to keep it facing out.
Select the line of the grid tool group.
In the drop-down menu, select the fixed needle tool, click on the left and right two points.
Fix them in 3D space.
In order to prevent the gusset from being unstable when rotating, first sew up the side of the same side after folding.
Set the sewing line type to Turned.
Because the sewing line type of Turned will automatically flatten, it will not bulge and affect the modeling.
Turn on the modeling.
Drag the fixed needle to wrap the gusset around the virtual model.
In the process of dragging, you need to change the perspective more to prevent the gusset from being misplaced due to visual deviations.
Because the board will be compressed a lot in the folding position, we can simulate this kind of compression by reducing the shrinkage.
Use the editing logic tool.
You can see that the board is in the direction of the gusset, and the arrowhead is in the forward direction, and the vertical axis is in the upward direction.
Now if we want to tie the knot, it must be compressed along the triangle direction, instead of changing the length of the gusset.
So here we choose to reduce the
Change after simulation, let the board shrink.
Gradually reduce the shrinkage to 60%.
Turn on the simulation.
Adjust the position of the fixed needle in the simulation process.
Slowly tighten the gusset.
Move theery down.
Make sure to tighten the gusset.
Next we will go back to the front.
Check if the position of the gusset is correct.
Because of the shrinkage, we need to leave some space in case it ciisked.
It is a point of JI Studio and dragway foil.
Fix the creases.
When the shape is more suitable and the neckline is not crooked, start to cut the plate.
It is more troublesome to manually cut in Marvelous Designer.
Usually, we will turn and make the cutting effect through the combination of multiple plates.
Click near the banana position on the two sides of the scarf, you can see the corresponding position in the 2D window.
Create an inner line near the corresponding position to cut the plate.
Copy and paste to the corresponding position on the other side.
If the inner line is not related to the outer line of the plate, then please select the outer line of the plate in the right-click menu.
Choose two inner lines.
Cut the seam allowance.
You can cut the seam allowance or cut the seam allowance.
At present, the two sides of the plate are sewed together.
In order to facilitate subsequent modifications, you can delete the seam allowance first and sew the large piece of the plate on the left and right sides together.
Form a ring and put it on the neck.
Reverse-activate the two small plates cut down.
Shift-Q can hide the plate.
Turn on the simulation and adjust the dress position.
The dress position can be modified by 100.
Confirm the scarf effect from the formal angle.
After that, we will fix the two small plates on the side of the back side and sew them together.
Otherwise, too many layers and folds will not be stable.
If the front panel of the freeze-dry is adjusted, if you have changed the filter, you can change it back.
Activate the two panels and display them.
Put the two panels in the right position.
In the video, I put the panels on one side of the 2D window together.
Look at the seam side.
First, we have to sew up the side of the plate with this fold.
Then we have to sew up the side that is close to the hanging part and the side after hanging.
Finally, add a knot in the middle and it's ok.
Put the inner line together with the outer line of the plate and add points.
In this way, when using the sewing tool, you can automatically identify the inner line and the side lines.
Then sew up the two panels on the top and bottom.
Note that the direction of the mark is the opposite, because it is folded.
Press the W key to click the panel at the 3D window.
The position of the click will be increased.
In order to prevent the subsequent instability, the folded sewing line will be changed to Turned.
And the sewing line will be changed to Turned.
The sewing line will be changed to Turned.
Now we have to make three lines.
All the sewing lines are the same.
Since we don't have a cut on the panel, we can't sew the line, so we change to Turned.
Now we have to make three lines.
In order to determine the length of the line, click the button to create a free sewing line.
Then, on the side of the panel, click the button to create another sewing line.
On the other side, click to create a sewing line on the other side.
Click on the blue support point to create a long sewing line.
Press W to click on the fixed needle that has been created, and you can delete the fixed needle.
And because the two panels are on the same side, it is also a gap, in order to prevent instability, it is better to change the type of sewing line to Turned first.
Unscrew the large panel and model it together.
The other side is also the same operation.
What should be the size of the DNA similarities or differences between the three panels?
In order to get the best fit, we will change the size of the DNA similarity to the size of the DNA.
To get the best fit, we will increase the size of the DNA similarity, and there is a maximum scale of the DNA, and we will also reduce the size of the DNA similarity.
For a more stable following simulation effect, reduce the particle diameter to 15 and increase the number of fabric faces,
and reduce the conflict thickness to 1.
The surface diameter around the virtual model is also reduced to 1,
reducing the air distance to be reserved.
After stabilizing, reduce the zoom to 40
to simulate the tightness.
Adjust the position of the fixed needle
so that the two small plates are always in a horizontal state.
Try not to hammer it too hard,
otherwise it will affect the cutting effect.
When using fixed needles to fix a certain part of the plate,
be sure that the plate is not stretched too much.
To make the position tighter,
we can apply elasticity to the line section.
We applied the shrink just now.
If the ratio of elasticity is higher than the ratio of shrink,
the elasticity will stretch the line section.
This is not right,
so we need to set a relatively small ratio.
Wait a minute.
In order to prevent the impact of the force,
we need to adjust the length of the line section.
The length of the line section
behind the
edge of the joint is limited.
If the width is not enough,
the joint may be pulled out.
This is not good.
In order to prevent the impact of the force
it is better to adjust the length of the line section.
Try not to work too hard.
We will start the basic production
in a few minutes.
This is what I have for you today.